<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelog>
  <version
    release="Sep 13,2021"
    version="1.5.1">
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the last playing track information would not properly persist.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where pressing the up volume button once would decrease the volume.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes a crash when attempting to send debug logs via the Feedback screen.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue that would cut the album title when in the album library tab.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue that would fail to properly sync album covers after the first sync.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Apr 13,2021"
    version="1.5.0">
    <feature>Adds radio station support.</feature>
    <feature>Adds support for album covers on the library albums, and tracks tab.</feature>
    <feature>Adds an auto-connect behavior when restoring the application to the foreground.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the volume up button would not work when volume was greater than 90%.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue that would cause the library search to hang after navigating view details. e.g. After going to
      album tracks.
    </bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the remote would continuously pause videos playing on the device.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Dec 22,2020"
    version="1.4.0">
    <feature>Adds statistics dialog when you can check how many tracks, etc are currently synced.</feature>
    <feature>Improves visual feedback when performing a library metadata sync.</feature>
    <feature>Adds a feedback message when queueing tracks/albums/genres/artists.</feature>
    <feature>Adds the ability to queue the album or artist when browsing the track list.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes a bug that would prevent users from queueing albums when browsing an artist's albums.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Dec 12,2020"
    version="1.3.0">
    <feature>Introduces the ability to change audio outputs.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes a bug with the feedback input being collapsed on smaller screen sizes.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes a crash while starting or stopping the background service.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Nov 26,2020"
    version="1.2.1">
    <bug>Fixes a background crash with the application service.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes a crash on cover retrieval.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue with the service discovery</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Nov 19,2020"
    version="1.2.0">
    <bug>Fixes a background crash with the application service.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Nov 07,2020"
    version="1.2.0-beta1">
    <feature>Adds support for Android 11.</feature>
    <feature>Improves the library metadata sync performance.</feature>
    <feature>Updates to the latest Material Design library.</feature>
    <feature>Integrates the library search functionality to the library screen.</feature>
    <removed>Removes the ability to hide the notification due to background execution limitations introduced in
      Android.
    </removed>
    <removed>Removes fast scrolling due to performance issues.</removed>
    <feature>Improves media integration with Android</feature>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Jan 25,2017"
    version="1.1.0">
    <feature>Some of the changes require v1.1.0 of the MusicBee Plugin to work.</feature>
    <feature>Refreshes the playlists along with the library data.</feature>
    <feature>Sorting now starts only from the triple dash icon in the now playing.</feature>
    <feature>Adds the option to enqueue all tracks and play the selected on the library track tab.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes the library search collapse that did not work previously.</bug>
    <feature>Reworks the default action option to affect only the track view.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes the query for showing the albums of an artist.</bug>
    <feature>Adds the option to show only album artists in the library view.</feature>
    <bug>Fixes the tab colors in the Help screen.</bug>
    <bug>Automatically scrolls to the playing track when entering the now playing screen.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the remote session volume slider wouldn't work.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes the ordering of the Genres to alphabetical.</bug>
    <feature>Adds fast scrolling to the library tabs.</feature>
    <feature>Adds Play Now (Queue All) option for albums.</feature>
    <feature>Pressing the track info on the main view should now open the Now Playing screen.</feature>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Dec 22,2016"
    version="1.0.1">
    <bug>Fixes a crash with a null extras payload when updating the widget.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes a crash with a null key event on the media intent handler.</bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the artist albums would not display properly.</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Dec 15,2016"
    version="1.0.0">
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the notification would not disappear on a connected wearable
      after closing
      MusicBee.
    </bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the volume control in the wearable notification would not
      work.
    </bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the temporary stop during track change would make the
      notification flicker.
    </bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where exiting the application through an other than MainActivity
      would navigate to the main activity.
    </bug>
    <bug>Adds a message on connection to inform the user in case an incompatible version of
      the plugin is used.
    </bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Dec 3,2016"
    version="1.0.0-beta.2">
    <bug>Fixes a potential crash caused by the progress updater</bug>
  </version>
  <version
    release="Nov 28,2016"
    version="1.0.0-beta.1">
    <feature>Requires v1.0.0 of the [a
      href="https://github.com/kelsos/mbrc-plugin/releases"]mbrc-plugin[/a]
    </feature>
    <feature>Changes minimum supported version to Android 4.1.x</feature>
    <feature>Optimizations on code</feature>
    <feature>Visual updateNotification of the application</feature>
    <feature>Replaces previous startup dialogs with Change Log</feature>
    <feature>Implements and optimizes a new library view</feature>
    <feature>Adds basic playlist support</feature>
    <feature>Merges Help and feedback views</feature>
    <feature>Uses new API to load covers.</feature>
    <feature>Uses new API to load lyrics.</feature>
    <feature>Users new API for Now Playing loading</feature>
    <bug>Fixes an issue where the application would start automatically on device boot
    </bug>
    <bug>Fixes an issue with the widgets that stopped to updateNotification after some time
    </bug>
    <feature>Increases the timeout of the automatic discovery function</feature>
    <feature>Adds extra actions on the Incoming call action [i](Stop and Pause along
      with Volume reduce)[/i]
    </feature>
    <feature>Reworks the connection settings detection functionality. [i](If the
      network allows it the detection should happen automatically on the application startup)[/i]
    </feature>
    <feature>Adds support for Debug logging</feature>
    <feature>Application now is written in Kotlin language</feature>
  </version>

</changelog>
